(Raj:)Half of it will be mine.
(Sheldon:)Do you need it
to buy a less disturbing sweater vest?
(Raj:)-Leonard, help.
-Are you kidding?
(Leonard:)I couldn't even talk him into giving me
one of his freaking napkins.
[SIGHS]
(Penny:)Wow, you really are a genius.
(Leonard:)Not really. I Googled how to do that.
(Leonard:)So listen....
(Leonard:)Have you ever made a pact
with someone?
(Penny:)You mean like a pinky swear?
(Leonard:)Okay, fine. Like a pinky swear.
(Penny:)In the first grade, my friend Rosie and I
made a pact to marry Bert and Ernie.
(Penny:)-You know, from Sesame Street.
-I'm familiar with Bert and Ernie.
(Penny:)Then we found out
we both wanted Ernie.
(Penny:)We didn't speak again
till middle school.
(Leonard:)Over puppets?
(Penny:)The heart wants what the heart wants,
Leonard.